(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
あれやこれや言いますから どうか探して見せて
I'll say this and that, so please try and find me
嘘と本音の間 うまく隠しといたんで
Because I've hidden well between lies and truth
ストリーミングハート
作詞・作曲 DECO*27
Streaming Heart
Lyrics & Composition: DECO*27
一人じゃダメなのどうして？
Why isn't it okay to be alone?
二人になればハッピー
If there's two of us, we'll be happy
そのうち二人が嫌で
Eventually we'll hate being together
一人がいいとか言って
And say it's better to be alone
せーの！仕様もない感情の
Ready! Where will these
行き着く先はどこでしょう
worthless emotions end up?
溺れそうになったら一緒に
If we're about to drown, together
深呼吸をぶつけ合おうな
let's crash our deep breaths together
どうもしちったね
I've done it now
落ちることが心地良くて
Falling feels so good
さぁ！
Come on!
アイマイにしたいのさ
I want to keep it vague
好きっていたって歪んで
Even if I say I love you, it's distorted
クラリ アイマイにしたいのさ
Dizzy, I want to keep it vague
嫌いになってしまえたら
If I could just learn to hate you
正解！
that would be the answer!
一人じゃダメなのどうして？
Why isn't it okay to be alone?
二人になればハッピー
If there's two of us, we'll be happy
そのうち二人が嫌で
Eventually we'll hate being together
一人がいいとか言って
And say it's better to be alone
どうせなら僕らもう一人
If we're going to be one anyway
だったらそれはそれでハッピー
then that would be happy enough in its own way
今日も僕が女の子
Today too, I'll play the girl
演じ合ってバカみたいさ
we're like fools playing roles together
いっそこのまま
I'd rather stay like this
朽ちながらも
even while rotting
辞められないのさ
I just can't stop
アイマイにしたいのさ
I want to keep it vague
好きっていたって歪んで
Even if I say I love you, it's distorted
クラリ アイマイにしたいのさ
Dizzy, I want to keep it vague
嫌いになってしまえたら
If I could just learn to hate you
正解！
that would be the answer!
タイガイにしたいのさ
I want to make it an exception
僕を奪い取ってから
After you've snatched me away
タイガイにしたいのさ
I want to make it an exception
もう、もう、もう！
More, more, more!
アレやこれや言いました
I said this and that
トカゲを吐き出して見せて
Show me by spitting out lizards
嘘と本音のあいだ
Between lies and true feelings
上手く隠しといたんで
I hid them well
逆卍 ラプラス・ダークネス 生誕祭 2022
Reverse Manji LaPlus Darkness Birthday Festival 2022
秘密結社集合
Secret Society Gathering
にっこにっこに～
Nikko Nikko Nii~
あーあー、っしゃー！マイクオッケー！
Ah, ah... Alright! Mic okay!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
ミニスカートで襲撃だ (ギュン!)
Attacking in a miniskirt (Jump!)
ギャップボイスで衝撃だ (ギュン!)
Shocking with a gap voice (Jump!)
恋の妄想　愛の暴走　待って待ってまほら (Don't stop!)
Love delusions, love rampage, wait, wait, mahora (Don't stop!)
だっだっだーい好き　こっくっくっ冗談
Da-da-da-da-I love you, jo-jo-jo-joke
ハクション！ だけど　クールに　ルーズにさせて
Bless you! But let me be cool and loose
ビバハピ / 作詞・作曲 Mitchie M
Viva Happy / Lyrics & Composition: Mitchie M
せつなくても　やるせなくても (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
Even if it's painful, even if it's helpless... (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
もう　あんな子になんて　なれないから (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
Because I can't be that girl anymore... (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
ありのままの自分を
Your true self...
愛せればケ・セラ・セラ
If you can love it, que sera sera
今は独りぼっちの君に
To you who are all alone now
歌をあげる
I'll give you a song
はい、どうぞ！
Here you go!
いやいや　争いは　嫌い主義　のののん
No, no, I hate conflict, no-no-non
ボロボロ　涙して　ヒトヨヒトヨニ　ヒトリゴト
Crying crumbling, talking to myself every single night
叱られても　急かされても (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
Even if I'm scolded, even if I'm rushed... (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
ダッシュで結果　求めすぎよ (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
You're asking for results too quickly with a dash (Viva Happy Viva Happy...)
常識はいつまでも
Common sense is always...
大人たちのスラング
the slang of adults
無意識の宇宙から君に
From the unconscious universe to you
届くサイン
a sign reaches
はい！
Hai!
クタクタ　睡眠不足　ハッ！　シンジガオ
Exhausted, lack of sleep, Ha! Serious face
アレコレ　したいけど　アイマイミマイン　ギリギリマイ
I want to do this and that, but I-My-Me-Mine, barely mine
ハッピーに振る舞う貴様らが...
You guys acting happy...
救われるわけねぇだろ！
won't be saved!
ちょっと純情なピーポー　ズタズタお悩み中
Slightly pure people, deeply worried
中途半端な御世辞お疲れ様！
Good job on the half-hearted flattery!
そんなに世間は甘くないんだから
The world isn't that sweet!
ワークハッピー　いい感じ　スルーでアポロゲティー
Work happy, feeling good, ignore with an apology
バーチャルなブーストベースでゴー！
Go with a virtual boost base!
いやいや　争いは　嫌い主義　のののん
No, no, I hate conflict, no-no-non
ボロボロ　涙して...
Crying crumbling...
そんなに世間は甘くない
The world isn't that sweet
ビバ！
Viva!
ホロコミックス！
Holo Comics!
吾輩の秘め恋のLOVE♡
My Secret Love ♡
～はやく俺に愛に恋よ、お前☆～
~Hurry up and fall in love with me, you☆~
秘密だぜ☆
It's a secret!
It's a secret☆
吾輩のヒミツのLOVE♡〜俺に惚れたらお終いな〜
My Secret LOVE ~It's over if you fall for me~
ラプラス・ダークネス
Laplus Darkness
私の名前はラプラス・ディア・ハイエスト・デス・サーティーン・ダイナ・アート・オブ・インパクト・サイン・オブ・ザ・ダークネス。
My name is Laplus Deer Highest Death Thirteen Dyna Art of Impact Sign of the Darkness.
今日は待ちに待った新学期！
Today is the long-awaited new semester!
大好きな俺くんと同じクラスになれるかな！？
I wonder if I can be in the same class as my beloved Ore-kun!?
お、俺くん... なんでなの... まさかこんなコトに...
O-Ore-kun... Why... I can't believe it's come to this...
ラプー、あんた呼ばれてるよ！
Lapu, someone's calling you!
ぐすっ... だれよこんなときに...
Sniff... Who is it at a time like this...
僕だよ。
It's me.
えぇー！！お、俺くん！？
Eeeh!! O-Ore-kun!?
吾輩に何か用ですか？
Do you have some business with me?
ラプちゃん、ちょっとこっちに。
Lapu-chan, come here for a bit.
ラプちゃん... 秘密を守れるかな？
Lapu-chan... can you keep a secret?
はい♡ もちろんです♡
Yes♡ Of course♡
命をかけれるのかな？
Can you put your life on the line?
い、命... だと...？
L-Life... you say...?
なに...？ この気持ち...
What is... this feeling...
おいどうなんだよ
Hey, what's it gonna be?
ねぇ！！何なの！！だれか教えてよ！！
Hey!! What is it!! Someone tell me!!
One two gets! 熱烈 watch you
One two gets! Passionate watch you
好き好きってはじけた Be my roulette
Bursting with 'I love yous', be my roulette
グッと迫ってドキッと
Drawing close, heart skipping a beat
痛い痛い痛い
It hurts, hurts, hurts
Emergency! ときめき over
Emergency! Heartbeat over-limit
一ミリの隙間にダイビング
Diving into a one-millimeter gap
ラブステップ全部コントロール
Controlling every love step
異常異常異常 せーの！
Abnormal, abnormal, abnormal, one-two!
だって今日はコンチメンタル
Because today is Continental
勇ましきチャレンジャー
A brave challenger
ちょっとだけセンチメンタル
Just a little sentimental
大好き大好き １２３はい！
I love you, I love you, 1 2 3 go!
マミムメモメモ見れないの
Ma-mi-mu-me-mo-mo, I can't look
タチツテトテトテが触れて
Ta-chi-tsu-te-to-te-to-te, we touch
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Love me right now, love me so much
もっとギュッギュッギュッと矯正録
More tight, tight, tight, correction log
あの子に寄りすぎてるハート
Your heart is leaning too much toward that girl
でもあの子の胸見透かさないで
But don't look through to her heart
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Love me right now, love me so much
私じゃないなんて What happened?
If it's not me, what happened?
One two gets! 見つけて watch you
One two gets! Find me, watch you
好き好きってカラフル cutie my roulette
Full of love, a colorful cutie, my roulette
ちょっと待って今射抜いた
Wait a second, I've just been shot through
嫌嫌嫌でも せーの！
No, no, no, but still, one-two!
だって今日はもっと求めて
Because today, I'm wanting more
麗しきチャレンジャー
A beautiful challenger
たったかいオートメーション
A single automation
大好き大好き １２３はい！
I love you, I love you, 1 2 3 go!
マミムメモメロにしてほしいの
Ma-mi-mu-me-mo, I want you to fall for me
ナニヌネコネコ 恋のコネクト
Na-ni-nu-ne-ko-ne-ko, love connect
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Love me right now, love me so much
もっとききききしゅきおせろ
More l-l-l-l-love, Othello
あの子マリオネット操れり
That girl is being handled like a marionette
でもそれもこれも悪くはないね
But even all of that isn't so bad
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Love me right now, love me so much
私じゃないなんて What happened?
If it's not me, what happened?
フレンドリーな振りして
Pretending to be friendly
周波数を満たさないで
Don't fill the frequencies
曰く付きの魅惑のリップ
Fascinating lips with a history
リアルになるピロ
Becoming real, pi-lo
マミムメモメモ見れないの
Ma-mi-mu-me-mo-mo, I can't look
タチツテトテトテが触れて
Ta-chi-tsu-te-to-te-to-te, we touch
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Love me right now, love me so much
もっとギュッギュッギュッと矯正録
More tight, tight, tight, correction log
あの子に寄りすぎてるハート
Your heart is leaning too much toward that girl
でもあの子の胸見透かさないで
But don't look through to her heart
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Love me right now, love me so much
私じゃないなんて What happened?
If it's not me, what happened?
まみむめもめもめも見れないよ
Ma-mi-mu-me-mo, I can't look at the memo
たちつてとてとてと手が触れて
Ta-chi-tsu-te-to, our hands are touching
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Fall in love with me, ASAP!
もっとギュッギュッキュートで攻めろ
Attack with more and more cuteness!
あのねくりよね透けてるハート
Hey, look, a transparent heart
でもねこの胸に透かさないで
But don't look through my chest
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ
Fall in love with me, ASAP!
私じゃないなんて終わってんね
If it's not me, you're finished!
（荒い息遣い）みんな...
(Heavy breathing) Everyone...
えっと、今日は...
Um, today...
吾輩の1周年ライブに...
to my 1st anniversary live...
来てくれてありがとうございます！
thank you so much for coming!
ちょっと待って... ちょっと待って...
Wait a second... Wait a second...
ちょっと...
Just a...
えっと、この衣装が...
Um, is this the first time...
みんなに見られるのは初めてかな？
everyone is seeing this outfit?
HoloXで、初めて...
In HoloX, for the first time...
1人目の新衣装は吾輩だよ！
I'm the first one with a new outfit!
トップバッター、常にトップ！
Top batter, always at the top!
常にナンバーワン！イェーイ！
Always number one! Yay!
笑うな... 笑わないでください...
Don't laugh... Please don't laugh...
ちょっと...
Wait a...
カメラマンが笑っちゃったので...
The cameraman laughed, so...
吾輩が気を取り直してやります。
I'll compose myself and continue.
ろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
ね、見てほしい。
Hey, I want you to see.
後ろにね、大きいリボンがありまして...
There's a big ribbon on my back...
吾輩の色の紫のリボンと...
A purple ribbon in my color, and...
謎の謎のところから出ている尻尾ね。
this tail from a mysterious place.
これ衣装のどこから出したのか...
I don't know where it's coming from...
自分でもよくわからないんだけど...
even I don't really know myself...
その、えっと、ごめんなさい。
Um, well, sorry.
あの、3曲...
Well, three songs...
3曲続けて歌ったから...
I sang three songs in a row...
ちょっとすごいことになってて...
so I'm in a bit of a state...
これ、これすごい尻尾がついてます。
This, this tail is attached.
尻尾がついてるって...
Saying it's "attached" sounds like...
ちぎってつけたみたい、違いますからね。
it was torn off and put on, but no.
デザイン、尻尾のデザインをね...
The design, for the tail design...
入れてもらいましたと。
I had them include it.
あの、枷が取れてません、ついてます。
Um, the shackles haven't been removed.
ということで。
So anyway.
足も見てほしいわ。
I want you to look at my legs too.
そう、相変わらずね、ここ...
Yeah, as usual, here...
マークが残ってるのと...
the mark is still here...
あと靴下をまた履き忘れていますね。
and I forgot to put on a sock again.
片方、どこかに忘れてきました。
One of them, I forgot it somewhere.
ちょっと、ロマンぐらいやめてください。
Hey, stop with the "romance" stuff.
ちょっとやめてくださいよ。
Please stop that.
「そんなつもりねぇよ」みたいな顔...
Making that face like...
やめろよマジで。
"I didn't mean it that way," stop it.
ということでね。
So anyway.
もうちょっと全身で撮ってもらおうかな。
Can I get a full-body shot?
一応ね、見たいでしょ、みんな？
Everyone wants to see, right?
可愛いポーズ取ってあげようかな、じゃあ。
Maybe I'll do a cute pose then.
可愛いポーズとかって、めちゃ無理された。
Being forced to do cute poses...
イェーイ！
Yay!
アイドルっぽい奴だね、アイドルっぽい。
That's very idol-like, isn't it?
きゃー！ きゃー！
Kyaa! Kyaa!
ちょっと恥ずかしい！
This is a bit embarrassing!
普通に恥ずかしい！ 止めて。
Just embarrassing! Stop it.
ちょっと待って。
Wait a second.
次、告知すること忘れました。
Next, I forgot to make an announcement.
この次に、ちょっとあの...
After this, there's a little something...
お披露目するものがもう1つあります。
one more thing I want to reveal.
こっちもね、みんなには...
This is also something...
まだ見せたことがないものなので...
I haven't shown everyone yet...
楽しみに待っていたら、と思います。
so please look forward to it.
だから、みんなまだ...
So everyone, please...
どこにも行かないで！
don't go anywhere yet!
きゃー！
Kyaa!
はい、じゃあ、よろしくお願いします。
Okay then, please stay tuned.
まだまだ見てね！
Keep on watching!
はぁ...
Sigh...
俺くん、こんな時間まで何してるんだろう。
I wonder what Ore-kun is doing at this hour.
結婚してから、もう4年。
It's been four years since we got married.
吾輩から俺くんへの愛は...
My love for Ore-kun...
年々増していっているというのに...
grows more and more every year...
俺くん、最近、全然構ってくれない。
but he doesn't give me any attention.
新婚の頃は、お仕事終わったら...
In our honeymoon phase...
すぐに帰ってきてくれたのにな。
he'd come home right after work.
今は「終電逃した」とか言って朝帰りばっかり。
Now he's always out until morning.
吾輩は家にいても暇だから、最近は...
I'm bored at home, so lately...
駅チカの24時間やってるカフェで...
I've been at this 24-hour cafe...
ひとり寂しくお茶して...
having tea all by myself...
おぉ、虚しいマジ。
Man, this is so depressing.
この時、ラプラス・ダークネスは...
At that time, La+ Darkness...
知る由もなかった。
had no way of knowing.
まさかこの後、あんなことが...
That after this, such a thing...
起きようとは。いや、本当にマジで。
was about to happen. No, seriously.
あれ？ もう1時。
Oh? It's already 1 AM.
帰ろうかな。眠いし。
Maybe I'll head home. I'm sleepy.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
俺くんが？！
Ore-kun?!
俺君が女を連れて、今、この店に、来店しているーー！
Ore-kun is here at this shop right now with a girl!
よ、こっ、こいつ何しに、あ、だめだ落ち着け。
W-Wh-What is this guy doing? Ah, no, calm down.
こいつガチで何しに来たんだ、あ、お、女とこんな夜中に。乾杯に、くそ、ああ！
What did he seriously come here for? A-And with a girl, at this time of night? A toast? Damn! Ah!
しかも、隣の席に座った！こいつ目ついてないのかよ！おい、妻が隣座ってますけど！
And they sat in the next booth! Is this guy blind?! Hey, your wife is sitting right next to you!
お、楽しくお話しを始めやがった。誰やこの女。店員を煽っている。
Oh, they're starting to have a pleasant conversation. Who is this woman? They're flirting with the waitress.
これは、あ、ま、また来てくださいね。何！？これはアフター！アフターです、乾杯。
It's like, 'P-Please come again.' What?! Is this an after-party?! It's an after-party. Cheers.
不健全だ。いや、でも他の女といるなんてダメだ！不健全だ！不埒だ！
How indecent. No, being with another woman is wrong! It's indecent! Outrageous!
なんの話をしている…パンケーキを食べに行く約束をしている！な！不健全だ！
What are they talking about... they're making plans to go eat pancakes! What?! How indecent!
こんな美女とパンケーキ、逆に不健全かもしれない。見えないほうがエロい的なやつかもしれない！
Pancakes with such a beauty—it might even be more scandalous. It might be one of those 'sexier when you can't see' things!
いや、なんで！他の女とパンケーキ食いに行くんだ、何故行くんだよ！吾輩とも食べに行ったことないのに！増す！
No, why?! Why are you going to eat pancakes with another woman? Why?! You haven't even gone with me yet! It's increasing!
許さん！許さん！パンケーキ、好きじゃないけど！吾輩別に好きじゃないけど！
I won't forgive you! I won't! I don't even like pancakes! I don't really like them, but still!
はー、はー、デートなんて許さない。俺君、女共々ぶっ殺す。かかってこい！
*Panting* I won't allow a date. Ore-kun, I'll kill both you and that woman. Bring it on!
おい！おい！おめぇだよおめぇ、俺君！何してんだこんなところで！
Hey! Hey! I'm talking to you, Ore-kun! What are you doing in a place like this?!
吾輩は毎日毎日お家で俺君が帰ってくるのをずーーーっと待ってんのに！
I'm at home every single day, waiting for you to come back all the tiーーーme!
この女、おんで、この女誰だよ！誰だよ！ねえ、なんか、なんか言えよおい！
And this woman—who is she?! Who is she?! Hey, say... say something, damn it!
ふざけんなよマジで、お前ら許せねえ。ここがお前らの墓場だ！
Seriously, don't mess with me. I won't forgive you two. This place will be your grave!
愛して愛して愛して
作詞・作曲 きくお
Love me, Love me, Love me
Lyrics/Composition: Kikuo
はるか遠い遠い昔　巻かれた首輪
A collar wound round long, long ago
人が欲しい　人が欲しいと叫ぶ　呪いの首輪
A cursed collar that screams for people, for people
怒らないで　見捨てないで　どこも行かないで
Don't be angry, don't abandon me, don't go anywhere
強く締める　吐くまで締める　人がいない　いないと
Tighten it hard, until I vomit, if there's no one, no one around
いい成績でしょう　ねえ　ねえ　いい子でしょう
I have good grades, don't I? Hey, hey, I'm a good child, right?
可愛い子でしょう　ねえ　ねえ
I'm a cute child, right? Hey, hey
いい子でしょう　苦しいね
I'm a good child, right? It hurts, doesn't it?
愛して　愛して　愛して　もっともっと愛して
愛して　狂おしいほどに
Love me, love me, love me, love me more and more
Love me, to the point of madness
苦しい　苦しい　呪縛を　解いて解いて　ねえ
It hurts, it hurts, break, break the curse, hey
止められない　ああ
I can't stop, ah
ねえ、吾輩っていい子だよね
Hey, I'm a good girl, right?
じゃあ、もっともっと愛してくれてもいいよね
So, it's okay for you to love me even more and more, right?
こっち見て
Look at me.
身体　身体　大きくなっても　小さい首輪
Though my body, my body grows, the collar stays small
苦しくなった　足りなくなった　人が　人が　足りない
It's become painful, it's not enough, people, people, they're not enough
クラスの誰にも負けない　綺麗ないい子でしょう
I'm a beautiful, good child, better than anyone in my class, right?
あの子よりも　どの
More than that girl, than any...
…どこよりも誰も彼も私を見てよ
...more than anywhere else, everyone, look at me.
あなたが好き、なの？
Do you like me?
聞きたいわ あなたが
I want to hear it, from you.
愛して 愛して 愛して
Love me, love me, love me,
全部あげる あなたに あなたに
I'll give you everything. To you, to you,
全部背負ってもらうよ
I'll have you shoulder everything.
足りない あなたが
It's not enough, you're...
足りない 離さないよ
...not enough, I won't let go.
ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
愛して 愛して 愛して
Love me, love me, love me,
もっともっと 愛して 愛して
more and more, love me, love me,
狂おしいほどに
to a maddening degree.
苦しい 離さない
It hurts, I won't let go,
苦しい もっともっとね
it hurts, more and more.
幸せなの
I'm happy.
はい、ということで
All right, so.
みんな見て！
Everyone, look!
これを見ろ！
Look at this!
ついに我も 3Dで
Finally, I too, in 3D...
脱げたぞー！
...have taken it off!
イェーイ！やったー！
Yay! I did it!
動くー！
I can move!
やっとですよ
Finally.
1年で、1年で成し遂げたこと
Something I've achieved in a year, in one year.
脱いだこと
Taking it off.
あー、このね お気に入りポイントはここです
Ah, this... my favorite point is here.
我が輩のネクタイを、このベルトの中に通してるっていうね
My tie is passed through this belt, you see.
たまに、あの、ファンアートとか描いていただいてる方で
Sometimes, those who draw fan art for me...
ここがどうなってるかわかんないみたいなのも見ましたけど
...I've seen comments like they don't know how this part works.
3Dではわかる、通ってるんですね 下を
In 3D, you can see it's passing underneath.
いいでしょ
It's good, right?
イェーイ！
Yay!
あともう一つある
And there's one more thing.
ここね、穴、ここから尻尾が
Here, the hole... the tail comes out from here.
ねえ、むずい… ここから尻尾が出てるんですよ
Hey, it's hard... the tail is coming out from here.
凄かったでしょ
Amazing, right?
あれ 我が輩の三面図ね なめくりまわすように見てた人たちならわかるかもしれないけどね
People who've looked at my three-view reference sheet inside out might already know, but...
今ライト層に向けてアピールしてますから
...I'm appealing to the casual fans right now.
いいでしょ
It's good, right?
イェーイ！
Yay!
いい感じ、ね 靴下がね 履いてない
Feels good. See, the socks... I'm not wearing any.
あ！ここ見てください
Ah! Please look here.
おおー！
Oh!
いいですか、こんな感じで皆さん
Is it good? Like this, everyone.
全身が見たい？全身が見たいみたいですね
You want to see the whole body? It seems you want to see the whole body.
どうですか
How is it?
イェーイ！イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
このブーツだね、ここ、ここ見てよ
These boots, here, look at this.
我が輩がこう自分の体を、見せたの初めてじゃないですか こうお披露目とかで
Isn't this the first time I've shown my body like this at a debut or something?
大体いつも「はい、こんな感じです イェーイ」秒で
Usually it's just, "Yeah, it's like this, yay," and it's over in a second.
初めてですね 大体なんかこういうお披露目配信にゲストで呼ばれて
It's a first. Usually, I'm invited as a guest to these kinds of debut streams...
一緒に写真撮ったりとかするんだけど
...and we take photos together.
自分の配信で、しかもMCやってないんですよ 我が輩 普段
But in my own stream... and I don't usually do MCing.
この1周年でやっとMCをするという
Finally doing MCing for this 1st anniversary...
偉業、偉業を成し遂げました
...I've achieved a feat, a great feat.
ということで 不慣れです
So, I'm not used to it.
はい、じゃあ写真撮ってください
All right, please take some pictures.
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、いいですか
All right, is that good?
普段ね 自分でも写真撮らないしね 人にもあまり撮られないんで
Usually, I don't take pictures myself, and I don't get them taken by others much...
貴重な機会
...so it's a rare opportunity.
イェーイ！ということで
Yay! So...
こ、こ、こんな感じで
...l-l-like this.
ハッシュタグなどつけてツイートすると いいかもしれないね
It might be good to tweet it with the hashtag.
はい、この後はですね
All right, after this...
ついに、ついにゲストパートです
...it's finally, finally the guest part.
今日はいろんな人に来ていただいておりますよ
We have various people coming today.
ということでね お楽しみにしててください
So, please look forward to it.
この衣装で 歌って踊るよ
I'll sing and dance in this costume.
見ててね
Keep watching.
じゃ、バイバイ！
Okay, bye-bye!
い〜やい〜やい〜や
作詞・作曲: Neru&z'5
I-ya I-ya I-ya
Lyrics & Composition: Neru&z'5
アラバスタ数年ぽしゃった
Alabasta, several years down the drain
この怠惰が憎いが
I hate this laziness, but...
またこうしてベッドでまた寝腐っている
I'm rotting in bed again like this
ここ最近調子は悪いが
My condition's been bad lately, but...
いや本気はまだまだ
No, my real power is still to come
そう言ったのはこれで何度目のセリフだろう
How many times have I said that line now?
無造作な部屋
A cluttered room
一重の両目
Single-lidded eyes
隠れ気は中の中の下
A shy spirit, at the bottom of the middle
恰好も体面
Appearance and face
身なりは三流
Dressed like a third-rate
お涙を頂戴
Please, give me your tears
僕ら有能じゃなーいさ
We're not competent, you know
だから終身刑でいいや
So, a life sentence is fine with me
のーてんきした
Carefree feelings
いーや いーや いーや
I-ya I-ya I-ya
混ざり合っちゃって
Mixing it all together
なんだっていいや
Whatever is fine
のーてんきした
Carefree feelings
いーや いーや いーや
I-ya I-ya I-ya
それで結構
That's good enough
段々降っていいや
It's okay to fall bit by bit
ほらセンチメンタル相まって
Look, combined with sentimentality
一千年のロケット
A thousand-year rocket
140文字のポエムに放っている
Releasing into a 140-character poem
こりゃ相当にバット決まった
This turned out quite bad
ならふて寝に決まりだ
Then it's decided, I'll sleep in a sulk
ただいつまでこうしてやり過ごすつもりだろう
Just how long do I plan to keep getting by like this?
負けるも吠えるも
Losing or howling
いないも同然
It's as if I'm not even here
逃げ足だけが得意の系
Good only at running away
エサを待つのみ
Just waiting for bait
口だけ達者
All talk and no action
獲物には即退散
Fleeing from prey immediately
おさまんないんだってばさ
It just won't settle down, I say
だから同情なんていーや
So, I don't need sympathy
のーてんきした
Carefree feelings
いーや いーや いーや
I-ya I-ya I-ya
混ざり合っちゃって
Mixing it all together
ぽんこつだっていいや
Being a piece of junk is fine too
のーてんきした
Carefree feelings
いーや いーや いーや
I-ya I-ya I-ya
それで結構
That's good enough
非道だっていいや
Even if it's heartless, it's fine
ほら完璧なやる気が崩れた
Look, my perfect motivation crumbled
またスマホをいじった
I fiddled with my smartphone again
ただこうしてベッドで死んだふりをしている
Just playing dead in bed like this
くたばったらいっそ楽ちんだ
It'd be easier if I just kicked the bucket
ならどうして死なない？
Then why don't I die?
そりゃ僕がこれっぽっちのヘタレだからだろう
That's probably because I'm such a coward
また噂のあいつがバズった
That guy in the rumors went viral again
まぁ正直ジェラった
Well, honestly, I was jealous
ただこうしてベッドで僕は腐っている
Just rotting in bed like this
ここ最近調子は悪いが
My condition's been bad lately, but...
いや本気はまだまだ
No, my real power is still to come
どうにでもこうにでもなってくれお釈迦様
Whatever happens, happens, Lord Buddha
のーてんきした
Carefree feelings
いーや いーや いーや
I-ya I-ya I-ya
混ざり合っちゃって
Mixing it all together
不毛だっていいや
Even if it's futile, it's fine
のーてんきした
Carefree feelings
いーや いーや いーや
I-ya I-ya I-ya
それで結構
That's good enough
段々降っていいや
It's okay to fall bit by bit
明日は頑張るといいや
I'll say I'll do my best tomorrow
だから今日はふて寝でいいや
So today, I'll just sleep in a sulk
ワンルーム・オール・ザット・ジャズ
作詞・作曲: DATEKEN
One Room All That Jazz
Lyrics & Composition: DATEKEN
独りきりのショータイム
A solo showtime
自己満足のパッション
Self-satisfied passion
誰も踏み込めない
Nobody can step in
私だけの空間
My own space
監督不在の
Director-less
自己完結のセッション
Self-contained session
誰も邪魔させない
I won't let anyone interfere
全ては自分次第
Everything is up to me
使い古したキーボード
A worn-out keyboard
カップに入れたコーヒー
Coffee in a cup
最高傑作のマイ・マスターピース
The greatest masterpiece, my masterpiece
他に何も要らない
I don't need anything else
好きなものは好きなだけ
As much of what I like as I want
拙い飾り立てて
Setting up clumsy decorations
この小さな部屋から
From this small room
今宵お届けします
Tonight, I'll deliver to you...
All That Jazz
動き始める皆の
Everyone starts moving
自己充足のパッション
Self-sufficient passion
ワンルーム・オール・ザット・ジャズ
One Room All That Jazz
バー、アドリブが試行錯誤、決まり回り
Bar, ad-libs of trial and error, spinning around.
独り回り始める自己肯定のセッション
A self-affirmation session that starts spinning on its own.
のべつまくなし推敲は遠回し
Constant revisions are just a detour.
使いまわしたキーワード
Reused keywords.
語彙の足りないリリック
Lyrics lacking vocabulary.
中途半端なヴォーカル、プライドはいらない
Half-baked vocals, I don't need pride.
だめなもんはだめなりに、あの手この手で組み上げて
If it's no good, I'll build it up in my own way, using every trick in the book.
綺麗なリボン重ねて、今日お届けします、ワンルーム・オール・ザット・ジャズ
Layering pretty ribbons, I'll deliver to you today, One Room All That Jazz.
触れてみたい秘密と
Secrets I want to touch and...
壊してみたい夜の中で
...inside the night I want to break.
間違いだらけの遊びしようよ
Let's play a game full of mistakes.
シニカルナイトプラン 作詞・作曲：Ayase
Cynical Night Plan / Lyrics & Composition: Ayase
ゲスト 天音かなた
Guest: Amane Kanata
別に意味とかないけどさ
It doesn't really mean anything, but...
眠い目をこする
Rubbing my sleepy eyes.
午前三時
3:00 AM.
君はまだ履き違えてる
You're still misunderstanding.
まあ間違えてる
Well, you are mistaken.
それであなたは誰なの
So, who are you?
どうしていたいの、痛いの、お互い様
What do you want to do? It's painful for both of us.
願うたびに名前を呼ばないで
Don't call my name every time you wish.
どうやったって見たいの、隠さないから
No matter what, I want to see it, because I won't hide it.
私のふりした私でよければどうぞ
If you're okay with me pretending to be me, go ahead.
塞ぐ目に落ちる景色のように
Like the scenery falling on closed eyes.
霞む私は誰のものでもないの
The hazy me doesn't belong to anyone.
バイ・マイ・セルフ、構わないで
By myself, don't mind me.
私だけに見せて、歪な夜を、どうぞ
Show only me the distorted night, go ahead.
ああもう本当にざっつ、やいやい
Ah, seriously, that's enough, hey hey.
どこの誰かと赤の信号、渡りゃいいでしょ
You can cross the red light with whoever you want, right?
だめだめだめってわかるでしょ
You know it's no good, right?
お利口さん待ってんのつまんない、やいやい
Waiting to be a good boy is boring, hey hey.
どこの誰かと赤の信号、渡りゃいいでしょ
You can cross the red light with whoever you want, right?
だめだめだめってわかるでしょ
You know it's no good, right?
お利口さん待ってんのつまんないよ
Waiting to be a good boy is boring.
ドクドク流れる泥沼、交わす言葉に絡めるシロップ
A pulsing quagmire, syrup entwined with the words we exchange.
早くドキドキさせてよほら、徘徊する誰かと私の得手
Come on, make my heart race quickly, my specialty with someone wandering around.
たまんないわ、いつものように、騙し騙され重なり合い
I can't stand it, as always, deceiving and being deceived, overlapping.
揺れるように、夢中に、あとはただ落ちるだけ
Like swaying, in a trance, and then just falling.
触れてみたい秘密と
Secrets I want to touch and...
壊してみたい夜の中で
...inside the night I want to break.
間違いを繰り返してさ
Repeating the same mistakes.
触れてみたい秘密を
Secrets I want to touch...
壊して知る夜の味を
...knowing the taste of the night by breaking it.
戻れないはじめましてをどうぞ
Go ahead, a "nice to meet you" that can't be taken back.
塞ぐ目に落ちる景色のように
Like the scenery falling on closed eyes.
霞む私は誰のものでもないの
The hazy me doesn't belong to anyone.
バイ・マイ・セルフ、構わないで
By myself, don't mind me.
私だけに見せて、歪な夜を、どうぞ
Show only me the distorted night, go ahead.
塞ぐ目に落ちる景色のように
Like the scenery falling on closed eyes.
霞む私は誰のものでもないの
The hazy me doesn't belong to anyone.
バイ・マイ・セルフ、構わないで
By myself, don't mind me.
私だけに見せて、歪な夜を、どうぞ
Show only me the distorted night, go ahead.
秘密の夜をどうぞ
Please enjoy this secret night.
赤坂アカ先生！書き下ろしイラストありがとうございます！
Akasaka Aka-sensei! Thank you so much for the newly drawn illustration!
え、ちょっとカッコいい感じの吾輩ということでね、
So, this is a slightly cool version of me.
この後歌う曲の雰囲気にも合わせて描いていただいております。
It was drawn to match the atmosphere of the song I'm about to sing.
勢いがいいっすね。
It's got a great sense of energy.
人何人かあやめてきたような雰囲気があります。
It has an atmosphere like I've just finished off a few people.
下手すぎる！感想言うのが下手すぎる！
I'm so bad at this! I'm so bad at giving my impressions!
いや、めっちゃ嬉しいです。ありがとうございます。
But I'm really happy. Thank you so much.
そして！なんと赤坂アカ先生の作品である...
And! Unbelievably, Akasaka Aka-sensei's work...
「推しの子」のアニメ化が決定したそうです！おめでとうございます！
...'Oshi no Ko' is getting an anime adaptation! Congratulations!
以前ですね、集英社さんとのコラボ配信で...
A while back, during a collaboration stream with Shueisha...
「推しの子」いいぞ！っていうのを話したことがあるんですけど、
...I mentioned how great 'Oshi no Ko' is.
今、メンバーがいてね、吾輩以外にも。うぉー！ってなっちゃってみんな。
Right now, there are other members here besides me. Everyone was like, 'Whoa!'
今のホロのメンツもうぉー！ってなってると思います。ありがとうございます。
I think the current Hololive members are also going 'Whoa!' Thank you.
そして、かぐや様は告らせたいはコミックス最終巻が、
And for 'Kaguya-sama: Love is War', the final manga volume...
12月19日、来月発売予定なので、
...is scheduled for release next month, on December 19th.
ぜひ貴様らチェックしてくれよな！
So make sure you all check it out!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
We always stood on the borderland I won't ever end up being from the cubes
意味深に並ぶNothing left to say
Profoundly lined up, nothing left to say.
誰もそんなに痛くはない。でも傷付けたくもない。
Nobody hurts that much. But I don't want to hurt anyone either.
手にとって確かめてた。きっと戻れないんだと知った
I checked it with my own hands. I knew I couldn't go back.
Borderland! Bye world!
Don't watch know! 思い上がった
Don't watch know! I got conceited.
Don't watch know! 仇となった
Don't watch know! It backfired.
Don't watch know! 優しさは仇
Don't watch know! Kindness is a curse.
We always stood on the borderland. 広げる両手でKeep balance
We always stood on the borderland. With outstretched hands, keep balance.
より高く跳べる方へ
Towards the side that can jump higher.
守りたいよ僕らの翼のないこの背中に
I want to protect it, on these backs of ours that have no wings.
背負ったReality and dream
Carrying reality and dreams.
何が正義だという。強さで固めた未来
What do you call justice? A future solidified by strength.
嘘だって変わらないさ。歯車は回り続ける
Even if it's a lie, it won't change. The gears keep turning.
Why's it? Bye dream!
You tell me! 哀しみに克て
You tell me! Overcome the sadness.
You tell me! 真実は何？
You tell me! What is the truth?
You tell me! 誠実の罠
You tell me! The trap of sincerity.
We always stood on the borderland. 風に吹かれて羽ばたく
We always stood on the borderland. Flapping wings in the wind.
生きてるうちに笑え
Laugh while you're still alive.
この世界の心が涙で不安だとしても
Even if the heart of this world is anxious with tears.
そこにはReality and dream
There lies reality and dreams.
Reality and dream
We always stood on the borderland. 広げる両手でKeep balance
We always stood on the borderland. With outstretched hands, keep balance.
より高く跳べる方へ
Towards the side that can jump higher.
変えられない僕らは翼のないこの背中に
We, who cannot change, on these backs of ours that have no wings.
背負ったReality and dream
Carrying reality and dreams.
We always stood on the borderland. 広げる両手でKeep balance. より高く跳べる方へ
We always stood on the borderland. With outstretched hands, keep balance. Towards the side that can jump higher.
We always stood on the borderland. 風に吹かれて羽ばたく
We always stood on the borderland. Flapping wings in the wind.
Ra pa pan pan pan...
Dark Breath
作詞：Co-Sho 作曲・編曲：小久保祐希
Lyrics: Co-Sho | Composition/Arrangement: Yuki Kokubo
Ra pa pan pan pan...
風穴開けたんだ 支配は始まった
I blasted a hole, the domination has begun
生き様かけたの バズコンの 自覚ないはずよ
I bet my way of life; you won't even realize the viral contest
抑え切れない 自制不能なパワー
Unstoppable, uncontrollable power
捕まえてみなよ 形もない My Heart
Try and catch it, my shapeless heart
I'm so crazy crazy love
半信半疑なその振る舞いは No No
That half-doubting behavior is a No No
心に誓って
Swear it on your heart
忠誠心見せてよ 今こそ
Show your loyalty, right now
Baby don't let me down
Ra pa pan pan pan...
カラダ目つき 癖になるでしょ
My body and gaze, they'll become a habit, right?
Ra pa pan pan pan...
ならず者 きり足りてないのよ Yeah
There aren't enough scoundrels, Yeah
Gossip more please 感じるでしょ
Gossip more please, you feel it, right?
革命的存在を
This revolutionary existence
It's God's Breath 渋滞感情 吹き去って
It's God's Breath, blow away the congested emotions
Ra pa pan pan pan...
浅はかな言葉 建前並べて
Lining up shallow words and pretexts
何もないことぐらい Baby I know
I know you've got nothing, Baby
ほら困るでしょ
See, you're in trouble, right?
枯れゆくこと受け入れた 鮮やかな Flower
A vibrant flower that's accepted its withering
知りながら贈る 笑顔に潜む姿
The figure hidden in a smile given while knowing
Really heavy heavy smile
心浸食される前に
Before your heart is eroded
その身を預けて
Entrust your body to me
目覚めさせるのよ 永遠に
I'll wake you up for eternity
I never let you down
Ra pa pan pan pan...
カラダ目つき 癖になるでしょ
My body and gaze, they'll become a habit, right?
Ra pa pan pan pan...
ならず者 きり足りてないのよ Oh no...
There aren't enough scoundrels, Oh no...
Gossip more please 感じるでしょ
Gossip more please, you feel it, right?
運命的衝動を
That fated impulse
It's God's Breath 内在細胞 酔わせて
It's God's Breath, intoxicate your inner cells
Ra pa pan pan pan...
時代 未来 なら見いだ 意外 じゃない I'm a genius
Era, future, then discover them; not a surprise, I'm a genius
全知 全能 Like a Jesus 巻き起こ
Omniscient and omnipotent like Jesus, I'll stir it up
待ちわびてたんだ 導くの全て
I've been waiting for this, I'll lead everything
I'm sorry
誰もが羨む 桃源郷へとアセンション
Ascension to the Shangri-La that everyone envies
Gotta be crazy crazy love
天才の常套手段はきっと 凡才には Special ね
A genius's standard tactics are surely special to the average
誰にも気付かれないけど
Nobody will notice, but...
手に入れるわ Dark Breath
...I'll get my hands on Dark Breath
Ra pa pan pan pan...
カラダ目つき 癖になるでしょ
My body and gaze, they'll become a habit, right?
Ra pa pan pan pan...
ならず者 きり足りてないのよ Yeah
There aren't enough scoundrels, Yeah
Gossip more please 感じるでしょ
Gossip more please, you feel it, right?
普通じゃない相当
It's quite unusual
It's God's Breath 六感かも 澄ませて
It's God's Breath, clear even your sixth sense
Ra pa pan pan pan...
あ、お待たせお待たせお待たせ。いや、ごめんね待たせちゃって。
Ah, sorry for the wait, sorry for the wait, sorry for the wait. No, sorry for making you wait.
え？そんな待ってないって？
Eh? You haven't been waiting that long?
うまいこと言うね本当に。あ、座るね。しょ。
You're quite the smooth talker, really. Oh, I'll sit down. There.
あ、じゃああの、早速さ、商品の説明に移らせてもらいたいんだけどさ。
Ah, well then, I'd like to get straight into the product explanation.
いやいやいや、全然怪しいものとかじゃないから。大丈夫、大丈夫。
No no no, it's not anything suspicious at all. It's fine, it's fine.
あ、今日のアジェンダはさ、あ、メールで言った通り、確実に君に幸せが訪れるっていうアイテムなんだけど。
Oh, today's agenda is, as I said in the email, an item that will definitely bring you happiness.
嘘じゃないって。本当に、話聞いてもらえばわかると思うからさ、ね？はい。
I'm not lying. Really, if you just listen, you'll understand, okay? Yes.
あ、じゃあ一つ目なんだけどさ。よいしょ。
Ah, well then, for the first one. Heave-ho.
商品①：限定ボイス＆壁紙セット
Product 1: Limited Voice & Wallpaper Set
はい。これ。これこれこれこれ。
Yes. This. This, this, this, this.
あ、Tシャツって顔してるよね。
Oh, you look like you're thinking "T-shirt."
ただのTシャツじゃないの。
It's not just any T-shirt.
あ、ちが、ちがうか。これ...
Oh, wait, no. This...
儀式さんっていう人にね、描き下ろしてもらった...
I had someone named Gishiki-san draw this...
ラプラス・ダークネスさんって知ってる？
Do you know La+ Darknesss-san?
知ってる？ あ、知ってる。おー、いいね。
Know her? Oh, you do. Oh, nice.
そう、ラプラス・ダークネスさんっていう人がデザインされたTシャツになってて、
Yeah, it's a T-shirt designed by La+ Darknesss-san,
チャンネル登録者が80万人、
And she has 800,000 subscribers,
80万人以上いるっていうあの配信者なんだよ。
She's that streamer with over 800,000 subscribers.
ただもんじゃないでしょ？
Not just your average person, right?
そう。そうなの。
Right. Exactly.
このインターネット時代、
In this internet era,
そう、バズマーケットのイニシアチブ握ってるって言っても過言じゃないわけよ。
Yeah, it's no exaggeration to say she holds the initiative in the buzz market.
しかも有名イラストレーターの儀式さんだからね。
And it's by the famous illustrator Gishiki-san.
ああ、これがね、ただのファングッズじゃなくて、
Ah, and this isn't just fan merch,
普段も着れるデザインになっててね、これがポイントなわけよ。
It's designed for everyday wear, and that's the key.
普段着にもよし、
Great as everyday wear,
で、イベントのときとか、プラスメイト同士のね、この...
And during events, among fellow Plusmates, this...
ファン同士の合図にもなれるわけ。この...
It can also serve as a signal between fans. This...
目と目でわかる。
You'll know just by looking at each other.
わかる？ これ。
You get it? This.
いいでしょ。つまりね、
Isn't it great? In other words,
消費者のインサイトに寄り添って設計されてるってことなんだよね。
It's designed with consumer insights in mind.
で、なおかつ、
And furthermore,
こう身に付けることでね、ファン同士の交流も拡大するっていうスキームになってるわけ。
By wearing it, it creates a scheme that expands fan interaction.
ね、いいでしょ。
Right, isn't it good?
で、これ。二つ目はね、
And this. The second one is...
二つ目はね、シルバーリング。
The second one is a silver ring.
これもね、チャンネル登録者80万人以上のラプラス・ダークネスさんがあしらわれたやつですね、これ。
This one also features La+ Darknesss-san, who has over 800,000 subscribers.
以上。
That's all.
あ、Tシャツと一緒でさ、なんか、
Ah, just like the T-shirt, it's like,
普段使いできるっていうか、日常に溶け込むって感じなわけ。
Something you can use daily, it blends into your life.
普段からラプラス総帥にアグリーしているプラスメイトのマストアイテムって感じなんだよね。
It's like a must-have for Plusmates who agree with Leader La+ every day.
わかる？ ほら。
You see? Look.
食べるのと一緒。息するのと一緒だよ。
It's like eating. It's like breathing.
これ、外見シンプルなんだけどね、
This has a simple exterior, but,
コンペティターとの差別化を明確にするために、内側にね、あの、
To clearly differentiate it from competitors, on the inside,
ラプラス総帥のね、尻尾のデザインが印刷されてるわけよ。
Leader La+'s tail design is printed there.
ただ、わかるものにはわかる。伝わるっていうかさ、
But those who know, will know. It gets the message across...
アジャイルで仲間意識湧いちゃうってわけよ。へへ。
And it creates a sense of camaraderie through agility. Hehe.
あ、ね。ここからが本題なんだけど、
Oh, and here's the main point,
なんと、この二つさ、セットで買えちゃうのよ。
You can actually buy these two as a set.
なんてったって、あの、どっちの商品もマーケットのニーズが...
Because, you know, the market needs for both products...
高いから。そうそうそう。
Are high. Right, right, right.
で、セットにはね、複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきちゃうのよ。
And the set comes with a postcard featuring a printed autograph.
で、しかも、しかもよ。
And, furthermore, furthermore...
数量限定で、直筆メッセージもあるんだって。やばいでしょ。やばいでしょ。
In limited quantities, there are even handwritten messages. Crazy, right? Crazy, right?
ちょ、大きい声出さないでよ。
Hey, don't talk so loud.
こんなでっかいビジネスの話ね、まだみんなに知られちゃまずいんだからさ。
A big business story like this... it's bad if everyone finds out yet.
ね。あ、ご、ごめんごめん。
Right? Oh, sorry, sorry.
で、あ、お値段？
So, oh, the price?
あー、鋭いね、君もね。
Ah, you're sharp, aren't you?
これ、セットで1万円くらい。1万円しないくらい。
This set is about 10,000 yen. A bit less than 10,000 yen.
コスパがやばいんだって、これ。へへ。
The cost-performance is insane. Hehe.
この商品が広まれば、幸せになる人たくさん出てくると思うわけ。
If this product spreads, I think a lot of people will be happy.
たくさん。で、君もその一人。そう。
A lot. And you're one of them. Yes.
この商品のステークホルダーは、僕と君だけじゃないってこと。
The stakeholders of this product aren't just me and you.
夢感じない？ ね、そうなのよ。だから...
Don't you feel the dream? Yeah, that's right. So...
あ、ごめん。あ、あ、あ、ごめん。
Oh, sorry. Oh, oh, oh, sorry.
ちょっと次のクライアントがさ、待ってるから。ちょ、行かない、行かないとね。
The next client is waiting. I have to go, have to go.
ごめん。
Sorry.
あ、貴重な時間ありがとね。ここ、会計しとくから。
Ah, thanks for your precious time. I'll take care of the bill.
あ、じゃあまた。あ、失礼しましたー。
Oh, well then, see you. Ah, excuse me!
活動1周年記念
11.26より販売開始
1st Anniversary
Sales start Nov 26
活動1周年記念フルセット
記念グッズ2種：Tシャツ、ぷらすめいとリング
1st Anniversary Full Set
2 Items: T-shirt, Plusmate Ring
フルセット購入特典
数量限定ver. 直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入りポストカード
Full Set Purchase Bonus
Limited Ed: Postcard with handwritten message & foil autograph
Tシャツ
イラスト：儀式　素材：綿
T-shirt
Illustration: Gishiki / Material: Cotton
1周年記念LIVE
1st Anniversary Live